Hello everyone. Accurate and
efficient diagnosis is crucial
in healthcare for medical
professionals and patients. Our
innovative application, MD
Vision, aims to revolutionize
the diagnostic process,
combining advanced technologies
with a user-friendly interface.
The core of MD Vision is our
powerful medical image captioner
module. Users can upload chest
X-ray images and our advanced
model extracts visual features,
outputting tags. These tags are
then fed into AI models top
produce detailed, highly
probable impressions and
findings. For medical
professionals, this
comprehensive approach provides
valuable insights, enabling
informed decisions and better
patient care. For patients,
this module is equally
important, helping them
understand their medical images
and know more about their
condition. Complementing the
image captioner is our
intelligent chatbot module,
Designed to benefit both medical
professionals and patients. For
providers, our system follows
carefully designed decision
trees, asking yes/no questions
to gather patient information,
narrowing down the
possibilities, and providing the
most likely differential
diagnoses. For patients, the
chatbot serves as a friendly
guide, helping them understand
their symptoms and potentially
underlying causes through an
interactive Q&A process.
Promoting Active Involvement in
Their Healthcare Journey: MD
Vision offers ease of use,
increased patient engagement,
and room for continuous
improvement to support more
medical imaging modalities and
diagnostic areas. Leveraging
cutting-edge technology and
prioritizing user experience,
MD Vision empowers accurate and
timely healthcare solutions for
medical professionals and